Guide to the Yale Events and Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of events and activities, 1950-circa 1994; Series II
  - Scholarships
    - Shafer Scholarships, 1979-1991 (Box 111, Folder 365)
    - Sterling Scholars, 1979-1987 (Box 111, Folder 366)
    - Scholarship "Winnie-the-Pooh" (Box 111, Folder 367)
    - Yale Alumni Association of Bergen County, NJ and Vicinity Scholarships, 1991 July (Box 111, Folder 368)
    - Yale Summer Sports Camps Scholarships, 1985 June (Box 111, Folder 369)
    - Yale Club of Eastern Fairfield County Scholarships (Box 111, Folder 370)
    - Yale Club of New Haven Scholarships, 1979-1989 (Box 111, Folder 371 - 372)
  - Sterling Memorial Library (SML)
    - Books, Letters, Papers (Box 112, Folder 373)
    - Boswell Papers (Box 112, Folder 374)
    - Building (Box 112, Folder 375)
    - Collections (Box 112, Folder 376 - 379)
    - Exhibitions (Box 112, Folder 380 - 382)
    - Holocaust, video testimonies (Box 112, Folder 383 - 385)
    - Kurzwell Reading Machine (KRM) (Box 112, Folder 386)
    - ORBIS (Box 112, Folder 387)
    - Preservation (Box 112, Folder 388)
    - Staff (Box 112, Folder 389)
    - Visitors from Sierra Leone, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 390)
  - Student Activities
    - Dance (Box 113, Folder 391)
    - Recreation (Box 113, Folder 392)
    - Classrooms (Box 113, Folder 393)
    - The Prom (Box 113, Folder 394)
    - Dormitories (Box 113, Folder 395)
    - Studying (Box 113, Folder 396)
  - Visitors to campus
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 397)
    - Dalai Lama, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 398)
    - Fallaci, Oriana, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 399)
    - Fonda, Jane, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 400)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 401)
    - Graves, Earl, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 402)
    - Haig, Alexander, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 403)
    - Kassenbaum, Nancy, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 404)
    - Kemp, Jack, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 405)
    - Kraus, Arthur with President Benno Schmidt, Jr., 1991 January (Box 114, Folder 406)
    - Lange, David, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 407)
    - Lanzmann, Claude, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 408)
    - Lear, Norman, 1977 (Box 114, Folder 409)
    - McCarthy, Mary, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 410)
    - Merrill, James, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 411)
    - Provost, visit, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 412)
    - Richardson, Elliott, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 413)
    - Shockley, William and Rusher, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 414)
    - Sullivan, Dr. Louis, Tetelman Lecture, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 415)
    - Quayle, Marilyn, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 416)
    - Villa-Lobos, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 417)
  - Volunteers
    - School Volunteers for New Haven, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 418)
    - Martin Luther King School (Box 115, Folder 419)
    - Lee High, Gifted Students (Box 115, Folder 420)
    - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute (Box 115, Folder 421)
  - Yale College
    - Introductory Information, 1989-1991 (Box 116, Folder 422)
    - Arts (Box 116, Folder 423)
    - Athletics (Box 116, Folder 424 - 425)
    - Classrooms (Box 116, Folder 426)
    - Dining Halls (Box 116, Folder 427)
    - Libraries (Box 116, Folder 428)
    - Residential Colleges (Box 116, Folder 429)
    - Speakers (Box 116, Folder 430)
    - Student Activities (Box 116, Folder 431)
    - Student Life (Box 116, Folder 432 - 433)
  - Yale University
    - 275th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 434)
- Slides and transparencies, circa 1974-1989; Series III
  - Volume I (Box 118)
    - Accelerator, 2 pages (Box 118)
    - Art and Architecture, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Aerials, Old Campus- David Ottenstein, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Aerials, 6 pages (Box 118)
    - Alumni, 3 pages (Box 118)
    - Art Gallery, 5 pages (Box 118)
    - Art School, 3 Slides (Box 118)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 5 Slides (Box 118)
    - Astronomy, Bethany Observing Station, 6 Slides (Box 118)
  - Volume II
    - Ballet Class, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Banners of Colleges, 2 pages (Box 118)
    - Battell Chapel, 2 pages (Box 118)
    - Becton Engineering and Applied Science Center, 2 pages (Box 118)
    - Belgium -- Reception for the King and Queen, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Beinecke Rare Books and Manuscripts Library, 6 pages; 3 slides (Box 118)
    - Bicycles, 5 slides (Box 118)
    - Blizzard '78, 5 pages (Box 118)
    - Branford College, 5 pages (Box 118)
  - Volume III
    - Campus Scenes, 18 pages (Box 118)
    - Commencement (Box 118)
    - Commons -- University dining hall, 2 pages; 3 slides (Box 118)
    - Communiversity Day, 1 page, Human chess game, 1981 (Box 118)
    - Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1 slide (Box 118)
    - Computer Center, 1 page; 1 slide (Box 118)
    - Connecticut Hall, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Cross Campus, 1 page (Box 118)
    - Cross Campus Library, 2 pages (Box 118)
    - Cullman Courts Tennis, 1 page (Box 118)
  - Volume IV
    - Davenport College, 7 slides (Box 118)
    - Divinity School, 2 pages; 6 slides (Box 118)
    - Dining Hall, 1 slide (Box 118)
    - Dormitory Rooms, 2 pages; 7 slides (Box 118)
    - Dramat, 6 pages; 3 slides (Box 118)
    - Durham Laboratory, 1 slide (Box 118)
    - Jonathan Edwards, 5 slides (Box 118)
    - Employees, 4 slides (Box 118)
    - Forestry, 3 pages; 2 slides (Box 118)
  - Volume V
    - Gibbs, Josiah Willard -- Laboratories, 4 slides (Box 119)
    - Graduate Studies, Hall of, 1 slide (Box 119)
    - Handsome Dan, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Harkness Gate, 5 slides (Box 119)
    - Harkness Tower, 6 pages (Box 119)
    - Harkness, William L., Hall, 7 slides (Box 119)
    - Hawaiian Vistors, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Health Services Center, 3 pages (Box 119)
    - Hewitt Quadrangle Bicentennial Buildings, 1 page; Caldor Sculpture, 6 Slides (Box 119)
    - Ingalls Rink, 6 slides (Box 119)
    - Interns -- New Haven Register, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Kline Biology Bat Project, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Kline Biology Laboratory, 6 pages (Box 119)
    - Kline Biology Tower,1 page; 4 slides (Box 119)
    - Kline Geology Laboratory, 1 page (Box 119)
  - Volume VI
    - Medical School Laboratory, 1 page; 4 slides (Box 119)
    - Morse-Stiles Colleges, 3 slides (Box 119)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick- Chubb Fellow, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - Mudd Library, 1 slide (Box 119)
    - Music -- Band, 3 pages (Box 119)
    - Music -- Marching Band, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - Music -- Bell Ringers Choir, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Music -- Glee Club, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - Music -- Miscellaneous, 2 pages; 4 slides (Box 119)
  - Volume VII
    - New Haven and Yale, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - New Haven Green -- Center Church,2 pages (Box 119)
    - Newman, Edward, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Old Campus, 5 pages (Box 119)
    - Osborn Memorial Laboratories, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Outdoor Sculpture, 2 slides (Box 119)
    - Peabody Museum, 3 slides (Box 119)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Phil's Barber Shop, 6 slides (Box 119)
    - Pierson College,1 page (Box 119)
    - Pierson-Sage Parking Garage, 1 slide (Box 119)
    - Power Plant, 3 pages (Box 119)
    - Protest '86 Schmidt Inauguration, 1 slide, Anti-apartheid (Box 119)
    - Repertory Theatre, 6 pages (Box 119)
    - Salute to New Haven, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Saybrook College, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - Scenics, 4 pages (Box 119)
    - School of Organization and Management, 5 slides (Box 119)
    - Security, 2 pages (Box 119)
    - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall, 1 page (Box 119)
    - Silliman College, 4 slides (Box 119)
    - Sprague Hall, 5 slides (Box 119)
  - Volume VIII, Sports
    - Basketball, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Crew, 7 slides (Box 120)
    - Exercise, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Fencing, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Field Hockey, 6 slides (Box 120)
    - Football, 9 pages (Box 120)
    - Golf, 2 slides (Box 120)
    - Ice Hockey, 5 slides (Box 120)
    - Sailing, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Skeet, 1 slide (Box 120)
    - Soccer, 1 page; 6 slides (Box 120)
    - Squash, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Swimming, 3 pages (Box 120)
    - Tennis, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Track, 5 slides (Box 120)
    - Water Polo, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Wrestling, 1 page; 7 slides (Box 120)
  - Volume IX
    - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, 1 slide (Box 120)
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine, 2 slides (Box 120)
    - Sterling Law Buildings -- Yale Law School, 5 pages (Box 120)
    - Sterling Memorial Library Courtyard, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Stiles College, 3 pages (Box 120)
    - Students, 11 pages; 2 slides (Box 120)
    - Street Vendor, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Symphony on the Green, 1 page (Box 120)
  - Volume X
    - Wiffenpoofs, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Women's Forum, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Woodbridge Hall, 3 slides (Box 120)
    - Woolsey Hall, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Yale Alumni Journal, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Yale Center for British Art, 9 pages (Box 120)
    - Yale Co-op, 4 pages (Box 120)
    - Yale Corporation, 2 pages (Box 120)
    - Yale Daily News, 2 pages; 3 slides (Box 120)
    - Yale Printing Services, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Yale Portraits -- Presidents, 3 pages (Box 120)
    - Yale Station, 1 page (Box 120)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital, 3 slides (Box 120)
  - Volume XI, Miscellaneous
    - Buildings, Faculty, Sculptures, 11 pages (Box 120)
  - Volumes XII-XIV, Commencement, 1974-1989 (Box 122)
- Oversize images, 1916; Series IV
  - Pageant -bicentennial of Yale in New Haven, 1916 (Box 121)
- Photographs attributed to Elliot and/or Eugene Kone, Circa 1942-1955; Accession 2005-A-087
  - Photographs attributed to Elliot and/or Eugene Kone, during their tenure with the Yale University News Bureau and the Audio Visual Center, Circa 1942-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
- Photographs of Mike Marsland, university photographer, documenting Yale University, 1977-2003; Accession 2009-A-070
  - A + A Exhibit [MM 314], 1995 March (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Acceptance Letters [hs 93], 1995 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Admissions -- Early Action Committee [mm 117], 1992 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions -- Undergrad, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Admissions -- Undergrad Minority Brochure [mm or JA 364], 1993 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action (Holloway and Stanley) [mm 5], 1992 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action (Holloway and Stanley) [mm 34], 1993 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action: Maxine Whitehead [mm 35], 1993 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action (Holloway/Stanley) [mm 429], 1996 October (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Aging Program [mm 68], 1993 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aging, Yale Program on Yale School of Medicine, 1999 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AIDS Grant [mm 465], 1997 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Needle Exchange Program
    - Yale van, 1991 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Yale van mural designed, painted by Mark Aldrich, 1991 July (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Albee, Edward: Visit to campus, 2000 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Albright, Madeleine K. [mm 377], 1996 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Joe Allen, Astronaut [mm 356], 1996 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Fund Workshop at Volvo [mm 45], 1993 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AYA -- Alumni Program [mm 344], 1995 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - America Reads' -- Rasco [mm 499], 1997 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Amistad /Union Gift, 2000 Summer (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AMPS Fellows: Summer Intern Program [mm 103], 1993 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ankle Diver: MTM, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Gravity Club [mm 440], 1996 September (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Anti-Smoking Poster Winners [mm 445], 1997 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Architecture Students: House Dedication, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Art Gallery -- Jock Reynolds [mm 504], 1998 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Art Gallery, Yale Univ: James Allen Photography Exhibit YBC, 1998 November 25 - 1999 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Art Gallery, Yale Univ. Photog. Dawould Bay, 1999 February 1-8 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - AA Gallery- miscellaneous photographs: Teacup Sculpture/Watches, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Art School Tour, Summer 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Aston Magna, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Athletics [mm 476], 1997 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Athletics (football) [mm 488], 1997 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Athletics Tutoring Program [mm 355], 1996 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - AYA Assembly -- Athletics [mm 362], 1995 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - AYA -- Yale Club of Northwestern Connecticut [mm 12], 1992 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - British Art Center (BAC) re-opening: Henry Moore Exhibit, etc., 1999 January 18-25 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bach Manuscript [mm 209], 1994 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bake Shop [mm 489], 1997 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Baker, James
    - With Levin, Circa 1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - with President Levin and Gus Ranis, 1999 October (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Robert D. Ballard [mm 513], 1998 March (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Barnes and Noble Executives [mm 450], 1997 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Barnes and Noble Interior [mm 496], 1997 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Baseball Camp: Summer [mm 214], 1994 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bass Center Dedication [mm 42], 1993 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Joseph Fogg and Basses, Circa 1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bass Center -- Exteriors [mm 122], 1993 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bass Building -- Interiors [mm 44], 1993 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Beacon School Press Conference [mm 218], 1994 July (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Beaver Pond [mm 431], 1997 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Tom Beckett (athletic director) News Conference [mm 96], 1994 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Beinecke Collections, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Beinart, Peter (at Master's Tea), 2000 October (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Berkeley College [mm 379], 1996 March (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Berkeley College tour, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Berkeley Divinity School -- Fall Convocation, 1992 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Bhatt, Ela (SEWA) [mm 373], 1996 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bicycle Safety, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bildner Prize Winners [jb 126], 1993 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bill Bradley's visit to Toad's, 2000 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Bio Action Lab Photos, 1999 November (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bio-ethics negatives (ALSO SEE "ISPS"), Circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Biospheric Institute: Board Meeting [mm 62], 1993 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Biospheric Studies -- Group Shots, 1992 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Black Expedition Movement: Ola Ray Nelson [mm 130], 1993 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Yale Book Store Opening, Circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Borgnine, Ernest (Master's Tea), 2000 October (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bosnian Library [mm 322], 1995 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bouchet and Mellon Fellows [mm 222], 1994 May (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bouchet Monument [mm 467.1], Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bouchet, Edward A. (also see Alumni file), Circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bouchet, Edward Memorial Tombstone, 1998 October (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Boutros Boutros-Ghali [mm 287], 1995 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bayer Center for Molecular Medicine: Exteriors (color prints) [mm], 1993 February (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bradley, Bill - Rally, Circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Braverman and Friedlander at Yale Center for British Art (YCBA) [mm 515], 1998 March (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - "Bright Beginnings" [mm 244], 1995 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - British Art Center -- Interiors [mm 101], 1993 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - British Art Center: Gift Shop, Circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - British Studies Colloquium, 1998 October (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - British Art Center: Conservation Lab, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - British Art Center: Gift by Donald Gallup: works of Edward Lear, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - BAC sculpture, Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - British Arts Center, Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Broadway Redesign Project, 2000 April (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Broadway -- Ribbon Cutting Ceremony [mm 332], 1995 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Broadway Tree Planting -- Memorial Park [mm 233], 1994 July 13 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Cleanth Brooks [mm 13], 1992 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Buffet, Warren, SOM visit, 1996 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Buildings
    - [mm 419], 1994 March (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - LC Hall Exterior, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Luce, Admissions [mm 419], 1996 September (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - New Environmental Sciences Facility: Groundbreaking, 1999 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Bulldog Day, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - President George W. Bush's Commencement Speech, 2001 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Business Expo [mm 238], 1994 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Buy in New Haven [mm 342], 1995 December (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - C-SPAN "School Bus" [mm 333], 1995 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Cabaret: Summer [mm 207], 1994 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Cadence Design Systems Inc. [mm 158], 1994 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Calhoun College [mm 349], 1995 September (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Marian Wright Edelman at Calhoun, 1999 October (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Calligraphy MTM, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Campus Construction, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Campus Earth Summit [mm 162], 1994 February 18-20 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Campus Tours [mm 475], 1997 October 13 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Carillon and Carilloneurs, 1994 March (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Carter, Kevin (at Master's tea), 2000 April (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Castle Lecture -- Paul Tsongas [mm 243], 1994 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Cello Group [mm 518], 1998 March (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Mary Chapin Carpenter [mm 255], 1994 November 4 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Chanukah Party [mm 255], 1994 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Child Development Campaign "I Am Your Child" Press: Announcement, 1997 April (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Children's Theatre, Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Child Study Center (groundbreaking), Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Christmas Gift Ideas [mm 495], 1997 December (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Chubb Fellowship, Circa 1990s
    - Blackmun [mm 288], 1995 January 28 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Walter Cronkite [mm 256], 1995 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Mayor Rudolph Giuliani [mm 254], 1995 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Jack Kemp [mm 446], 1997 April 15 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Shimon Peres [mm 454], 1997 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Rowland [mm 345], 1995 November 8, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 126 - 127)
    - C. Todd Whitman [mm 279], 1994 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Citizen's Jury [mm 151], 1994 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Joshua Civin (alderman) [mm 252], 1994 October 27 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Clinton Visit, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 131 - 132)
  - Coca-Cola Gift [mm 6], 1992 October 27 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Coffin Fellows [mm 306], 1995 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Community Relations
    - Coats for Kids [mm 56], 1993 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Sheila Wellington and Michael Adanti [mm 131], 1992 August 13 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Community Rowing, Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Presidents Community Service Dinner [mm 8], 1993 March (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Community Service Awards [mm 153], 1994 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Community Service Event [mm 386], 1996 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - President's Community Service Reception, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Communiversity Day [mm 149], 1994 April (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Communiversity Day [HS 296], 1995 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Communiversity Day [mm 461], 1997 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Communiversity Day 1999 Yale Bulletin and Calendar (YBC), 1999 May 3-17 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Communiversity Day, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Communiversity Day, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Communiversity Day, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Computer Center/ Barnes + Noble [mm 508], 1998 February (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Connecticut Technology Council [mm 247], 1994 November 7 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Construction Shots (Misc), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Cooperative High School [mm 478], 1997 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Cosby, Bill [MTM], 2000 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Costume Shop [MTM], 2000 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Cozza, Carm, Press Conference [mm 392], 1996 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Croatian President Visit, 2000 September 15 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Cronkite, Walter, "With Malice Toward None" [mm 11], 1993 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Cultural Diversity Training (Medical Students with Dr. Bia), 1999 September (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Cutler, Lloyd, Visit to Yale Law School YBC, 1999 May 3-17 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - DNA Research [mm 491], 1997 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Dance Class, in Payne Whitney Gym (PWG): B.Todi, Drama Student, YBC, 1999 March 29 - April 5 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Dance Symposium, Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Davies Mansion [mm 509], 1998 February 26 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - DaVane Lecture Series [mm 409], 1997 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - DeVane Lecture/Anthony Kronman, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Dias, Jack [mm 457], 1997 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Dining Hall Chefs Master Workshop, 1999 January (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Dining Hall Workers [mm 449], 1997 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Dining Halls -- Various, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Disabilities Fair, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Divinity School Construction MTM, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Divinity School Convocation [mm 89], 1994 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Divinity School -- Richard Wood [mm 427], 1996 December (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Do Downtown Magic Shaw, 1999 October (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Richard Dorfman's Retirement [mm 33], 1993 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Duffy, Tom: Civil War Monument [mm 124], 1993 January 26 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Dwight College (Family Tree Print), Circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Dwight-Edgewood Neighborhood [mm 237], 1994 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Dwight School Groundbreaking, 2000 June (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Early Action Days [mm 271], 1995 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Earth Observation Laboratory [mm 7], 1994 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Economic Impact [mm 74], Fall 1993 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Elementary Sports Clinic [mm 302], 1995 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Elihu Yale's 350th Birthday: Beinecke Plaza, 1999 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Elihu Yale portrait, Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Elm-Ivy Awards and Sterling Scholars, 1993 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Elm/Ivy Recipients [mm 228], 1994 May 25 (Box 3, Folder 187 - 188)
  - Elm/Ivy Recipients [mm 313], 1995 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Elm Ivy: Group Shot, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Elm and Ivy Awards: Suzanne Jovin, 1999 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Employees Day -- Yale Bowl [mm 231], 1994 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Employees Day -- Yale Bowl [mm 336], 1995 September 16 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Employee Day [mm 469], 1997 September 20 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Yale Bowl Employee Day, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Engineering and Applied Science: Undergraduate and Graduate Brochures, 1992 July 17 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Engineering Laboratory Dedication, 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Environmental Fellows [mm 444], 1997 March (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Environmental Writer's Conference [mm 4], 1992 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Equestrian Center [mm 452], 1996 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Equestrian Center [mm 403], 1996 July 18 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Esterling, Grant, Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Fall Foliage Tour [mm 341], 1995 October (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Fan Fellows, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Farmington Canal Press Conference [mm 468.1], 1998 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Fencing Championship [mm 367], 1996 March (Box 3, Folder 206)